Finding Aid for Stanford R. Ovshinsky papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Business Administration, 1943-2009
  - Energy Conversion Devices, Inc.
    - Promotional videos and media, 1993-2002 (Box 97)
      - Ovshinsky/Stempel interview, undated (Box 106)
      - "The Road to the Sun: Alternative Energy for the Americas,", 2009; video
      - "The Road to the Sun: Alternative Energy for the Americas" production binder, University of California Berkeley/HKO Media, February 13, 2009 (Box 96)
      - "Sunlaw Cogeneration Partners 1," Sunlaw/Bosustow Video, June 7, 1990; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
    - Publicity and media coverage (Box 104)
      - "Alaska Report,", September 25, 1996; VHS videocassette) (Box 104)
        (includes electric car and interview Robert Stempel)
      - Blieden, February 7, 1983; U-matic videocassette (Box 104)
        (H. Richard Blieden)%ne interview, Channel 7
      - "The Bloomberg Forum," Robert C. Stempel, Chairman/CEO, Interview, September 15, 1998; VHS videocassette (Box 104)
      - Bloomfield Community Television, "Michigan on Wall Street" with Stan Ovshinsky and Robert Stempel, January 1997; VHS videocassette (Box 105)
      - Bush, George H.W. and electric car reports: News 7, WJLA TV, October 25, 1991/Cable News Network (CNN) Weekend News, October 26, 1991; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
      - Cable News Network (CNN) footage, October 19, 1987; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
      - Channel 56 video, VHS videocassette (Box 94)
      - "ECD Analysts Video,", April 20, 1998; Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 95)
      - ECD News Program Channel 7, Channel 55, VHS videocassette (Box 95)
      - ECD/USSC (United Solar Systems Corporation) press conference, February 14, 1996; VHS videocassette (Box 95)
      - ECD/USSC (United Solar Systems Corporation) 5 Mega-Watt Opening, February 15, 1996; VHS videocassette (Box 95)
      - "Edge--CNBC Cable, Energy Conversion Devices,", February 22, 2000; VHS videocassette (Box 95)
      - "Electric Vehicles," Cutting Edge Technology Report, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 95)
      - "Energy Efficient House," Headline News Network, October 23, 1996; VHS videocassette (Box 95)
      - GM Advanced Technology Vehicles Press Conference at North American International Auto Show, highlights, January 4, 1998; video
      - GM Battery, Energy Conversion Devices, March 18, 1994; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
      - GM EV1 Global Motors and ECD Press Conference and Tour Highlights with Lee Iacocca, dated, April 16, 1998; video
      - GM EV1 Global Motors and ECD Press Conference additional footage, dated, February 10, 1998; 2 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 89)
      - GM Ovonic Auto Show Display, dated, January 13, 1998; (2 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 89)
      - GM Ovonic, TV 2 News, December 1, 1994; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
      - "Hidden Tech," Target 7 News, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
      - "La Luz de La Esperanza," Documental Oaxaca, undated; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 97)
      - "Market Call," CNN/FN Cable, May 21, 2002; VHS videocassette (Box 104)
        (featuring Robert Stempel)
      - "Ovonic Energy Solutions,", November 19, 2008; Sony DVCAM videocassette (Box 94)
      - "Ovonic Hydrogen Solutions Demonstration," White House Television, February 6, 2003; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 95)
      - "Ovonic Hydrogen Solutions in the News, ", February 6-11, 2003; February 24, 2003; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 95)
      - "Ovonic Information Technology Solutions,", February 13, 2003; video
      - "Ovonic Solar Solutions" in Mexico, July 3, 2002; video
      - Ovonics/Robert Stempel, CEO, WDIV First News at 6, August 22, 2003; VHS videocassette
      - PV Shingles from United Solar on WDIV, February 1996; VHS videocassette (Box 94)
      - Rural Electrification Program, Oaxaca, Mexico, 2000; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
      - Saraboo Production/ECD, June 18, 1986; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
      - United States Department of Energy/Energy Conversion Devices press conference, January 18, 1994; VHS videocassette (Box 106)
      - US Advanced Battery Consortium (USABC)/Energy Conversion Devices (ECD)/Ovonic Battery press conference, May 19, 1992; VHS videocassette (Box 89)
      - "What's Up in Technology?" Thirteen/WNET, October 23, 1998; VHS videocassette (Box 89)
      - White House Conference on Global Climate Change, excerpt of Secretary Pena's holding and discussion, USSC Solar Shingle, October 6, 1997; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
    - Research (Box 53)
      - Active material fabrication basic process, June 1973; 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Affidavits -- missing sample 644, August 1978 (Box 53)
      - Amorphous Silicon, 1994-1995 (Box 53)
      - Cosmology collaboration with Fritzsche, 1992-2003; 2 folders (Box 53)
        (Includes research for papers: The Origin of Dark Matter in the Universe and Vacuum Energy, Gravity, and an Approach to Combing General Relativity with Quantum Mechanics)
      - Memory materials-Ge:Sb:Te, 1992-2005 (Box 53)
      - Optical recording, 1999-2000 (Box 53)
      - Posters, undated (Box 53)
      - Properties of amorphous semiconductors at high temperatures, October 1969 (Box 53)
    - Resumes, undated (Box 53)
    - Schedules, 1968-1969 (Box 53)
    - Shareholders
      - Annual reports
        - 1968-1976 (Box 53)
        - 1993 (Box 53)
      - Financial reports, 1962-1985 (Box 53)
      - Interim reports, 1970; 1985 (Box 53)
      - Letter to shareholders
        - 1979 (Box 53)
        - 1994 (Box 53)
        - 1995 (Box 53)
        - 1996 (Box 53)
        - 1997 (Box 53)
        - 1999 (Box 53)
        - 2000 (Box 53)
      - Meetings, 1985 (Box 53)
      - Miscellaneous, 1981-1983 (Box 53)
        (Includes an organizational hierarchy)
      - Presentation to shareholders' meeting, 2005; video
      - President's letter (Box 53)
        - 1981 (Box 53)
        - 1983 (Box 53)
        - 1983 (Box 53)
        - 1985 (Box 53)
        - 1987 (Box 53)
        - 1988 (Box 53)
        - 1990 (Box 53)
        - 1992 (Box 53)
        - 1993 (Box 53)
      - Special reports, 1972-1996 (Box 53)
    - Speeches and interviews, 1969-1982 (Box 54)
    - SRO employment agreement and termination, 1993-2007
      - Stock options, 1996-2006 (Box 54)
        (Contains Iris Ovshinsky's employment agreement)
    - Stock share prices, 2007-2011 (Box 54)
    - Subsidiaries
      - Grupo Ovonics Latinoamerica, 2003-2004 (Box 54)
      - Micorovonics -- Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 54)
      - Ovonic Battery Company
        - Advanced development, 2002-2005 (Box 54)
        - Advance MH alloys, October 2001(?) (Box 54)
        - American Natural Resources Company annual reports, 1983-1984 (Box 54)
        - Chevy Volt meeting, April 2007 (Box 54)
        - Cobasys-Information binder, 2006 (Box 54)
        - Correspondence-Unhappy corporate partners, December 1996 (Box 54)
        - Development and meeting PowerPoints, 2007 (Box 54)
        - Development and strategy, 1990-2000(?) (Box 54)
        - Foreign storage and material cost, 1994-1998 (Box 54)
        - Fritzsche, Hellmut, July 1998 (Box 54)
        - GM Ovonic
          - April 1994 (Box 54)
          - 1997 (Box 54)
        - License agreement, April 1995 (Box 54)
          (Walsin Tech. Corp.)
        - Matsushita hydrogen storage alloy patent, June 1989 (Box 54)
          (Effect on ECD)
        - Meeting with ECD, February 21-22, 1996 (Box 54)
        - Memos, 1997 (Box 54)
        - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 54)
        - Presentation slides, undated (Box 54)
        - Review meeting-NIST --AMAPP, July 15, 1999 (Box 54)
      - Ovonic Display Systems -- presentation slides, undated (Box 54)
      - Ovonic Hydrogen Technology, 1997-2002; 2 folders (Box 54)
      - Ovonic Hydrogen Technology, 2000-2003; 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Ovonic Hydrogen Systems
        - Texaco Ovonic Hydrogen Systems, LLC, 2003; photographs (Box 55)
        - Ovonic Solid Hydrogen Storage System Challenge Bibendum ( September 23-25) photographs, 2003
        - Texaco Ovonic Hydrogen Systems manufacturing facility design, 2003 (Box 110)
        - Highlights: Texaco, Inc., and Energy Conversion Devices, Inc., press conference, May 2, 2000; video
        - Texaco and Energy Conversion Devices, Inc., press conference additional footage (display materials and reporter reactions), May 2, 2000; 2 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 89)
        - Texaco/ECD presentation with Stanford Ovshinsky, June 7, 2000; VHS videocassette (Box 106)
        - Texaco Hydrogen Economy Corporate Center meeting, June 22, 2000; VHS videocassette (Box 106)
        - Akron, 2006 (Box 55)
        - Akron groundbreaking, April 27, 2006 (Box 55)
        - Akron meeting, June 13, 2006 (Box 55)
        - Acquisition, 2007-2008 (Box 55)
        - Business model and proposal to purchase, 2007 (Box 55)
        - ECD Ovonics Press Conference in Akron, (two videos), April 27, 2006; .ZIP file
      - Ovonic Imaging Systems, Inc. (Box 55)
        - Report -- New concepts and applications in nonsilver photographic and electrographic recording, undated (Box 55)
        - Shareholders
          - Annual reports, 1987 (Box 55)
          - President's letter, 1989 (Box 55)
        - X-ray -- Perspectives on Medical Imaging internal memo, 1973-1974 (Box 55)
      - Ovonic Media, LLC
        - 1990-2001 (Box 55)
        - 2000 (Box 55)
      - Ovonic Memories, Inc. -- Switch memory, 1970-1973 (Box 55)
      - Ovonic Solar -- marketing strategy slides, undated (Box 55)
      - Ovonyx
        - 2006, 2 folders (Box 55)
        - 2007, 2 folders (Box 55)
        - 2008-2009, 2 folders (Box 55)
        - 2010-2011 (Box 56)
        - 2012 (Box 56)
        - Acquisition, 2007 (Box 56)
          (by Ovshinsky Innovation)
        - Correspondence and Cognitive computer patents, 2000-2002 (Box 56)
        - Fritzsche problem solving, August 2000 (Box 56)
          (Contains research photographs)
        - Ovonic Cognitive Computer
          - 1992-2000 (Box 56)
          - 2000-2005 (Box 56)
          - Abstracts and revisions, 2003 (Box 56)
          - Board meeting posters, May 8, 2003 (Box 56)
          - Cognitive device principles of operation, July 2003 (Box 56)
            (B. Pashmakov, superseded by Intel pkg. Aug 26, 2003)
          - Cognitive quantum computing, 1992-2000 (Box 56)
          - Encryption, 1998-2000 (Box 56)
          - History, undated (Box 56)
          - Information binders
            - Confidential, 1999(?) (Box 56)
            - Ovonic Cognitive Computer (OCC), 2003 (Box 56)
          - Meetings
            - Logic devices -- 3-terminal devices, January 5, 2004 (Box 56)
            - M. Cohen, February 17, 2004 (Box 56)
          - Miscellaneous, 2004-2006 (Box 56)
          - Number of constant amplitude pulses (Box 56)
            (added cog comp file, Sept 2003)
          - Overheads, 2002-2005 (Box 56)
          - Package to Intel, August 2003 (Box 56)
          - Presentations, 2004-2007 (Box 56)
          - Proposals
            - Business version, April 2005 (Box 56)
            - Conceptual plan, January 2006 (Box 56)
            - Revisions, February 2005 (Box 56)
            - Short, long, and Intel versions, February, April 2005 (Box 56)
          - SRO paper drafts, 2003-2006 (Box 56)
        - Press releases, 2003-2008 (Box 56)
      - Sovonics (Box 94)
        - Plant 11 opening video, May 31, 1984; U-matic videocassette (Box 94)
        - Photovoltaic plant dedication ceremony, May 31, 1984 (Box 56)
        - Presentation slides, undated (Box 56)
        - Press release and patents, 1985 (Box 56)
        - "Power Where You Need It,", March 29, 1986; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
        - Recent application photographs, 1988 (Box 56)
        - Report on solar technology, 1986(?) (Box 56)
        - Status of Amorphous Silicon Alloy solar technology at ECD, 1986 (Box 56)
      - Uni-Solar (Box 97)
        - ASR Metal Roofing on HGTV, May 14, 1998; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 97)
        - Business plan review, 2005 (Box 56)
        - Inauguration forum schedule, June 24, 2002 (Box 56)
        - Information packet, 2004 (Box 56)
        - Correspondence, November 1997 (Box 107)
        - Distribution and installation of Uni-Solar Unikits in Chiapas, Mexico, October 1994; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
        - Installation of solar panels on the Mir space station, November 1998; VHS videocassette (Box 95)
        - Management report, 2007; includes Research and Development department (Box 56)
        - Opening and groundbreaking, June 2002; July 14, 2005 (Box 56)
        - Opening photographs, June 2002; .ZIP file
        - ECD/Uni-Solar Groundbreaking Ceremony and Plant Tour, produced (video is also labeled August 15, 2005), August 16, 2005; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
        - Samuel Bodman ECD/Uni-Solar speech, August 29, 2005; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
        - ECD Uni-Solar Groundbreaking film, July 14, 2005; video
        - ECD Uni-Solar (Greenville, Michigan) press video and visit of President Bush, March 21, 2006; video
        - ECD Uni-Solar Tour and History, July 5, 2010; video
        - ECD Mexico/Uni-Solar PVL training installation, dated, June 3, 2002; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 89)
        - Origin, 1990-2001 (Box 57)
        - Reports, 2010-2011 (Box 57)
        - Research and correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 57)
        - Research and development, 2007-2008; and drift reduction results (Box 57)
        - Shingle roofing products, undated (Box 57)
        - United Solar Sytems: "The Power to Change the World,", February 11, 1998; VHS videocassette (Box 57)
        - United Solar Systems, Inc., compilation reel, May 28, 1998; VHS videocassette (Box 95)
    - Technical reports, 1965-1966 (Box 57)
    - Technical reports, 1970-1973; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Working files, 1973-1984 (Box 57)
    - Working files and notes -- SRO, 1971-1985 (Box 57)
    - Visit of Stan and Iris Ovshinsky, and "entourage" to Soviet Union, circa 1985-1986; VHS videocassette (Box 105)
    - Visit of Russian delegation to ECD, January 1991; VHS videocassette (Box 104)
    - Visit to Russia, July 1990; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
  - Institute for Amorphous Studies (IAS)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 57)
      - Committee member list, 1983(?) (Box 57)
      - Committee member list and Institute history, September 1985 (Box 57)
      - Photographs of committee members, March 1984 (Box 57)
        (Contains negatives)
    - APS satellite meeting, March 1984 (Box 57)
    - Board of Directors
      - Board member list, undated (Box 57)
      - Meetings (Box 58)
        - January 4, 1984 (Box 58)
        - January 3, 1986 (Box 58)
      - Minutes
        - January 1983, March 1984 (Box 58)
        - January 1983-April 1984 (Box 58)
        - August 1984-February 1985 (Box 58)
        - January 1985 (Box 58)
        - December 1986 (Box 58)
      - Photographs of board members, 1984 (Box 58)
    - Brochures
      - 1982-1986 (Box 58)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 58)
        (Contains photographs, negatives, and slides)
    - Conferences
      - General information, 1983; 1985 (Box 58)
      - International conference on the Theory of the Structures of Non-Crystalline Solids, 1985 (Box 58)
    - Correspondence
      - International topical conference on Transport and Defects in Amorphous Semiconductors (TODIAS)
        - Journal of Non-Crystalline Solids, July 1984 (Box 58)
        - Lecture transcripts, March 1984 (Box 58)
        - Photographs, March 1984 (Box 58)
      - Advisory Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 58)
      - Board of Directors, January 1983-November 1985; 2 folders (Box 58)
      - Bogden, Al, August-September 1984 (Box 58)
      - Corporate communications, November -- December 1984 (Box 58)
      - Events at the Institute, May 1982-November 1985 (Box 58)
      - Ito, Rik, January-September 1985 (Box 58)
      - Miscellaneous, March 1982-August 1984 (Box 58)
      - Ovonic Battery Company, March 1985 (Box 58)
      - Ovshinsky, Stanford, January 1985-November1986, 2 folders (Box 58)
      - Schwartz, Brian, August 1984-May 1987 (Box 58)
        (Director)
      - Steele, Martin, October 1982-June 1984 (Box 58)
      - Requests for information, October 1984-September 1985 (Box 58)
    - Energy Conversion Devices (ECD)
      - Corporate Values and Operating Principles, September 1985 (Box 58)
      - Miscellaneous typing done for ECD personnel, 1984 (Box 58)
      - Project listings, January 1985-May 1986 (Box 58)
      - Rosenfield and Clevey
        - Miscellaneous correspondence, November 1984-August 1985 (Box 58)
        - National Science Foundation science week, October 1984-March 1985 (Box 58)
        - Science and technology exhibit, November 1984-December 1985 (Box 58)
      - Small business innovation research proposals, October 1986 (Box 58)
      - Summer intern program, April-September 1985 (Box 58)
    - Events, January 1985-June 1986 (Box 58)
    - Financing, September 1984-February 1987 (Box 58)
    - Future programs, July-August 1985 (Box 58)
    - Inauguration, April 1982
      - Attendance and Mott dinner party (Box 58)
      - Photographs (Box 58)
      - Press release (Box 58)
      - Transcript of opening remarks (Box 58)
      - Write-ups (Box 58)
    - Institute for Amorphous Studies series
      - Volume 1
        - Correspondence with authors, July-November 1984 (Box 59)
        - Correspondence with board of directors, September 1984 (Box 59)
        - Correspondence with publisher and contract, June 1984-February 1985 (Box 59)
        - Dust jacket and cover, January-February 1985 (Box 59)
        - Index, undated (Box 59)
        - Proofs and permission for publication, June 1984-January 1985 (Box 59)
      - Volumes 2 & 3
        - Correspondence with publisher and contracts, November 1984-August 1985 (Box 59)
        - Mott, Nevill Festschrift, October 1985 (Box 59)
        - Schedule sheet, September 1984 (Box 59)
        - SRO paper, November 1984 (Box 59)
      - Future Volumes, January 1984-July 1985 (Box 59)
    - Institute photographs, undated; 3 folders (Box 59)
      (Contains photographs and negatives)
    - Jordan College Energy Institute, 1985 (Box 59)
    - Lecture series
      - Abstracts, 1982-1983 (Box 59)
      - Announcement posters, 1982-1986 (Box 111)
      - Announcement posters, 1989-2010 (Box 112)
      - Attendance lists, 1982-1984 (Box 112)
      - Correspondence miscellaneous, 1984-1986 (Box 112)
      - Recorded lectures
        - September 29, 1982--Adler, David, "Physics of Amorphous Semiconductors", 2 VHS videocassettes (Box 98)
        - October 14, 1982--Kastner, Mark, VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - December 8, 1982--Fritzsche, Hellmut, "Determination of the Density of States in Amorphous Semiconductors", VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - December 20, 1982--Lucovsky, Gerald, "Vibrational Properties of Amorphous Solids--a) Elements and Compounds b) a-Si alloys", VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - April 6, 1983--Pankove, Jacques, VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - September 28, 1983--Boolchand, Punit, "Massbauer Spectroscopy in Amorphous Semiconductors", VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - October 24, 1983--Boolchand, Punit, VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - November 6, 1983--Zallen, Richard, "Percolation Theory: A Model for All Seasons" (tape has duplicate label reading Prof. Beinenstock), VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - 1984--Moustakas (likely Theodore), VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - June 14, 1984--Goldstein, Bernard, 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 98)
        - June 1984--Conrad, Michael, 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 98)
        - July 11, 1984--Magar, Roger, U-matic videocassette (Box 98)
        - July 26, 1984--Chakraverty, B.K., 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 98)
        - Cohen, Morrel, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - Crandall, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - Desmarteau, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - Guha, Subhendu, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - Henisch, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - Taylor, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - Thorpe, Michael, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - Pankove, Jacques, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 98)
        - October 25, 1984--Cooper, Leon, 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 99)
        - November 29, 1984--Twarog, Betty "Oxygen Deficiency Can Control the Form and Function of the Lung Circulation", 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 99)
        - December 6, 1984--Williamson, Samuel J., "Neuromagnetism Lecture", 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 99)
        - January 3, 1985--Moss, Si, 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 99)
        - January 17, 1985--Loferski, U-matic videocassette (Box 99)
        - February 28, 1985--Pohl, 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 99)
        - March 6, 1985--"Atomic Comics", 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 99)
        - March 21, 1985--Tsu, Raphael, 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 99)
        - April 11, 1985--Grieg, 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 100)
        - April 19, 1985--Jean Bennett, 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 100)
        - May 15, 1985--Greenler, Robert, 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 100)
        - May 22, 1985--Schuller, Ivan, VHS videocassette (Box 100)
        - June 13, 1985--Levanthal, Marvin, "Matter and Anti-Matter at the Center of the Milky Way Galaxy", VHS videocassette (Box 100)
        - September 20, 1985--Wilson, Robert Rathbun, "Art, Intuition, and Science", 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 100)
        - November 1, 1985--Pellier, U-matic videocassette (Box 100)
        - November 22, 1985--Hoffmann, Roald, "Moving from Discrete Molecules to Extended Structures: A chemical and Theoretical Approach to Solid State", VHS videocassette (Box 100)
        - December 9, 1985--Hartman, Hy, "Spin Glasses, Clays, and the Origins of Life", VHS videocassette (Box 101)
        - January 6, 1986--Davis, Edward A., "21st Birthday of Amorphous Materials", 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 101)
        - January 17, 1986--Cronin, James, "Do the Macroscopic and Microscopic Assymetries [sic] Have the Same Origin?", VHS videocassette (Box 101)
        - February 21, 1986--Frankel, Richard, "Magnetic Navigation in Bacteria and Algae", 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 101)
        - March 4, 1986--Fitzpatrick, Nigel, "The Aluminum Air Battery", 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 101)
        - March 14, 1986--Schumaker, Bryan P., "Through History With Comet Halley", VHS videocassette (Box 101)
        - April 21, 1986--Pauling, Linus, U-matic videocassette (Box 101)
        - April 28, 1986--Mott, Nevill, "The Mobility Edge Since 1969", VHS videocassette (Box 101)
        - June 10, 1986--Edgerton, Harold, "Strobe Lights and Their Use", VHS videocassette (Box 101)
        - June 20, 1986--Bell, James W., "Fuzzy Messages, Real Stuff, and the Denial of the Importance of Science and Technology at the Dawn of the Information Age", U-matic videocassette (Box 101)
        - August 1, 1986--Henke, Burton L., U-matic videocassette (Box 101)
        - September 3, 1986--Turnbull, David, "Phase Transitions and Metastability in Condensed Ge and Si", U-matic videocassette (Box 101)
        - October 8, 1986--Sze, Simon M., "Fundamental Limits of VSLI Devices", VHS videocassette (Box 101)
        - October 29, 1986--Henisch, Heinz K., "Photographic Pleasures", U-matic videocassette (Box 101)
        - November 19, 1986--Axelrod, Daniel, "Star Wars: Offense or Defense?", U-matic videocassette (Box 101)
        - December 3, 1986--Carroll, Robert G., "Cancer Detection and Treatment with Monoclonal Antibodies", U-matic videocassette (Box 101)
        - March 17, 1989--Adcock, Willis, "The Manufacturing Challenge", VHS videocassette (Box 102)
        - November 19, 1990--Weisskopf, Victor, "The Origin of the Universe", VHS videocassette (Box 102)